A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1981-1990 FA402
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1989; 0.5 Cubic Feet 38 microfilm reels (35mm); 38 Reels 38 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - United States of America, 1989; 1989/200
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, 1989 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - United States Environment Protection Agency (Hoffman, John S.), 1989 (Reel 28, Frame 26)
    - United States Information Agency (G-P), 1989 (Reel 28, Frame 29)
    - United States Institute of Peace, 1989 (Reel 28, Frame 33)
    - United States Zululand Educational Foundation (Barham, William T.), 1989 (Reel 28, Frame 41)
    - University of California (A-W), 1989 (Reel 28, Frame 43)
    - University (C), 1989 (Reel 28, Frame 299)
    - University (F-L), 1989 (Reel 28, Frame 701)
    - University (M), 1989 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - University (N-T), 1989 (Reel 29, Frame 324)
    - University (V-Z), 1989 (Reel 29, Frame 652)
    - U, 1989 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - V-Wa, 1989 (Reel 30, Frame 300)
    - We, 1989 (Reel 30, Frame 743)
    - Wh-Wi, 1989 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - World (F-W), 1989 (Reel 31, Frame 189)
    - Wo-Wr, 1989 (Reel 31, Frame 449)
    - Youth Action Program (Stoneman, Dorothy), 1989 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - Youth Service America, 1989 (Reel 32, Frame 166)
    - Y-Z, 1989 (Reel 32, Frame 353)
  - Philippines, 1989; 1989/242
    - A-S, 1989 (Reel 32, Frame 709)
  - Argentina, 1989; 1989/301
    - B-C, 1989 (Reel 32, Frame 789)
  - Brazil, 1989; 1989/305
    - C-N, 1989 (Reel 32, Frame 813)
  - Costa Rica, 1989; 1989/313
    - Tropical Agriculture Research and Training Center, 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
  - Cuba, 1989; 1989/315
    - Public Health (Menchacha, Roberto), 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 77)
  - Honduras, 1989; 1989/321
    - Zamorano (Semerad, Kate), 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 79)
  - Mexico, 1989; 1989/323
    - M-N, 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 81)
  - Peru, 1989; 1989/331
    - Parades A., Pedro G., 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 117)
  - El Salvador, 1989; 1989/333
    El Salvador
    - Centro Salvadoreno de Tecnologia Apropiada, 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 122)
  - England, 1989; 1989/401
    - A-U, 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 151)
  - Ireland, 1989; 1989/403
    - International Federation of Surgical Colleges (MacGowan, W. A. L.), 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 341)
  - Scotland, 1989; 1989/405
    - E-U, 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 387)
  - Australia, 1989; 1989/410
    - B-N, 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 409)
  - Bermuda, 1989; 1989/421
    Bermuda
    - Chadu Organization, 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 670)
  - Canada, 1989; 1989/427
    - C-U, 1989 (Reel 33, Frame 674)
  - Jamaica, 1989; 1989/437
    - Gayle, Golda, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
  - India, 1989; 1989/464
    - A-T, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 4)
  - Bengal / Bangladesh, 1989; 1989/466
    - Planning Commission (Population Development and Evaluation), 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 192)
  - Burma, 1989; 1989/468
    - Than Swe, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 201)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1989; 1989/472
    - A-S, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 204)
  - Kenya, 1989; 1989/476
    - African Centre for Technology Studies (Juma, Calestous), 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 235)
  - Malawi (Nyasaland), 1989; 1989/482
    - Chipeta, C., 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 242)
  - Rhodesia, 1989; 1989/483
    - A-U, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 286)
  - South Africa region, 1989; 1989/487
    - King Moshoeshoe II of Lesotho, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 410)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1989; 1989/489
    - S-U, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 424)
  - Uganda, 1989; 1989/492
    - K-M, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 579)
  - West Africa, 1989; 1989/495
    - P-W, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 713)
  - Nigeria, 1989; 1989/497
    - Nigerian Popular Theatre Alliance, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 744)
  - France, 1989; 1989/500
    - C-V, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 752)
  - Ivory Coast, 1989; 1989/527
    - A-U, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 946)
  - Senegal, 1989; 1989/531
    - African Regional Centre for Technology (Thomas, Babatunde), 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 973)
  - People's Republic of China, 1989; 1989/601
    - C-S, 1989 (Reel 34, Frame 975)
  - Taiwan, 1989; 1989/605
    - Xie Shaoping, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 1)
  - Japan, 1989; 1989/609
    - C-P, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 25)
  - Thailand, 1989; 1989/617
    - C-T, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 102)
  - Holland, 1989; 1989/650
    - I-U, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 131)
  - Indonesia, 1989; 1989/652
    - Matepe Foundation, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 175)
  - Ethiopia, 1989; 1989/701
    - United Nations, Economic Commission for Africa (Nana-Sinkam, S. C.), 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 177)
  - Austria, 1989; 1989/705
    - Neuspiel, Ernst, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 200)
  - Belgium, 1989; 1989/707
    - C-U, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 208)
  - Germany, 1989; 1989/717
    - B-F, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 281)
  - Tanganyika (Zambia), 1989; 1989/723
    - Tanganyika (Zambia) - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1989; 1989/723.D
      - Sokoine University of Agriculture (L-M), 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 309)
  - Zambia, 1989; 1989/724
    - K-M, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 371)
  - Cameroon, 1989; 1989/735
    Cameroon
    - University of Yaounde (Pondi, Jean-Emmanuel), 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 428)
  - Hungary, 1989; 1989/750
    - Hungarian Academy of Sciences (Dudits, Denes), 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 431)
  - Italy, 1989; 1989/751
    - G-N, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 438)
  - Norway, 1989; 1989/767
    - B-H, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 458)
  - Russia, 1989; 1989/785
    - M-S, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 465)
  - Finland, 1989; 1989/787
    - University of Helsinki (Swaminathan, Madhura), 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 547)
  - Spain, 1989; 1989/795
    - C-I, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 554)
  - Sweden, 1989; 1989/800
    - Hammerskjold, Knut, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 628)
  - Switzerland, 1989; 1989/803
    - I-W, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 635)
  - Cyprus, 1989; 1989/809
    - Agriculture (Ministry of ), 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 694)
  - Saudi Arabia and Oman, 1989; 1989/817
    - King Faisal Foundation, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 709)
  - Palestine / Israel, 1989; 1989/825
    - I-P, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 745)
  - Lebanon, 1989; 1989/833
    - Beirut University College, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 764)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE) - Biotechnology Career Fellowships, 1989; 1989/860
    - An Chung Sun, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 766)
  - Members and Meetings, 1989; 1989/903
    - E-M, 1989 (Reel 35, Frame 768)
  - Humanities, 1989; 1989/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1989; 1989/911.E
      - A-B, 1989 (Reel 36, Frame 1)
      - Ca-Ci, 1989 (Reel 36, Frame 309)
      - Columbia College (Resident Fellows), 1989 (Reel 36, Frame 505)
      - Co-H, 1989 (Reel 37, Frame 1)
      - John Carter Brown Library (Resident Fellows), 1989 (Reel 37, Frame 392)
      - Kent State University (Resident Fellows), 1989 (Reel 37, Frame 741)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Resident Fellows), 1989 (Reel 37, Frame 801)
      - Michigan State University (Resident Fellows), 1989 (Reel 38, Frame 1)
      - N-O, 1989 (Reel 38, Frame 560)
- General Correspondence, 1990; 0.38 Cubic Feet 29 microfilm reels (35mm); 29 Reels 29 microfilm reels (35mm)
  - International, 1990; 1990/100
    - Goldmark, Peter C., Jr. (Speeches), 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - B-K, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 293)
    - L-Y, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 385)
  - Administration - Applications for Employment, 1990/101
    - Applications for Employment - Agricultural Programs, 1990; 1990/101.01
      General note
      Series mark-up is written 101-1.
      - A-Y, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 581)
    - Applications for Employment - Arts Program, 1990; 1990/101.02
      Series mark-up is written 101-2.
      - Pirau, Vasile, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 814)
    - Applications for Employment - Health and Sciences Program, 1990; 1990/101.03
      Series mark-up is written 101-3.
      - A-Z, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 823)
    - Applications for Employment - Social Science Program, 1990; 1990/101.06
      Series mark-up is written 101-6.
      - A-W, 1990 (Reel 1, Frame 947)
    - Applications for Employment - Administration - General, 1990; 1990/101.07
      Series mark-up is written 101-7.
      - A-D, 1990 (Reel 2, Frame 1)
      - E-K, 1990 (Reel 2, Frame 290)
      - L-M, 1990 (Reel 2, Frame 514)
      - N-R, 1990 (Reel 2, Frame 665)
      - S-Z, 1990 (Reel 2, Frame 814)
    - Applications for Employment - Administration - Financial, 1990; 1990/101.08
      Series mark-up is written 101-8.
      - Croy, Bonni Brownlee, 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
    - Applications for Employment - Population Sciences, 1990; 1990/101.12
      Series mark-up is written 101-12.
      - A-O, 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 8)
  - Requests for Information, 1990; 1990/102
    - Directories, 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 22)
  - International Organizations, 1990; 1990/103
    - International (C-I), 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 26)
    - United Nations, World Health Organization (C-W), 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 555)
    - United Nations Conference on Environment and Development, 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 758)
    - United Nations Environmental Program (Tolba, M. K.), 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 762)
    - United Nations International Children's Education Foundation, 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 766)
    - United Nations Research Institute for Social Development, 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 768)
    - A-I, 1990 (Reel 3, Frame 803)
    - P-W, 1990 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
    - International Organizations - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1990; 1990/103.D
      Agriculture; Fellowships
      - International Board for Plant Genetic Resources, 1990 (Reel 4, Frame 188)
  - IPP (International Potato Program), 1990; 1990/107
    - International Potato Program (Genetic Engineering), 1990 (Reel 4, Frame 196)
  - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas, 1990; 1990/118
    - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas, 1990 (Reel 4, Frame 199)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 1990; 1990/120
    - 120, 1990 (Reel 4, Frame 202)
    - C-T, 1990 (Reel 4, Frame 246)
  - Greater Voice for Africa in the United States (Africa Policy Watch Project), 1990; 1990/121
    - A-K, 1990 (Reel 4, Frame 287)
    - M-W, 1990 (Reel 4, Frame 656)
  - Population Sciences (PS) - Reproductive Biology or Contraceptive Development, 1990; 1990/199
    - LaGuardia, Katherine, 1990 (Reel 5, Frame 1)
  - United States of America, 1990; 1990/200
    - Ab-Ah, 1990 (Reel 5, Frame 6)
    - Al, 1990 (Reel 5, Frame 329)
    - American Journal of Agricultural Economics (Barry, Peter J.), 1990 (Reel 6, Frame 1)
    - American (A-W), 1990 (Reel 6, Frame 399)
    - American Public Radio - Volume 2, Number 1, 1990; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15958)
    - Am-Au, 1990 (Reel 6, Frame 770)
    - Ba-Bi, 1990 (Reel 7, Frame 1)
    - Bl-Br, 1990 (Reel 7, Frame 357)
    - Bu, 1990 (Reel 7, Frame 561)
    - C-Ca, 1990 (Reel 8, Frame 1)
    - Ce, 1990 (Reel 8, Frame 378)
    - Ch-Ci, 1990 (Reel 9, Frame 1)
    - Cl-Col, 1990 (Reel 9, Frame 444)
    - Com, 1990 (Reel 9, Frame 678)
    - Con-Cor, 1990 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Council (A-R), 1990 (Reel 10, Frame 264)
    - Cow-Cy, 1990 (Reel 10, Frame 809)
    - D, 1990 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - E, 1990 (Reel 11, Frame 359)
    - Fa-Fi, 1990 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Fl, 1990 (Reel 12, Frame 114)
    - Foundation (A-M), 1990 (Reel 12, Frame 360)
    - Fo-Fu, 1990 (Reel 12, Frame 691)
    - Ga-Ge, 1990 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Gl-Go, 1990 (Reel 13, Frame 127)
    - Gr-Gu, 1990 (Reel 13, Frame 330)
    - Harvard (L-U), 1990 (Reel 13, Frame 577)
    - Ha, 1990 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - He, 1990 (Reel 14, Frame 101)
    - Hi-Ho, 1990 (Reel 14, Frame 591)
    - Hu, 1990 (Reel 14, Frame 681)
    - I, 1990 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - J, 1990 (Reel 15, Frame 384)
    - K, 1990 (Reel 15, Frame 686)
    - La-Le, 1990 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Me-Mi, 1990 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Mo-Mu, 1990 (Reel 17, Frame 297)
    - National (Ac-As), 1990 (Reel 17, Frame 489)
    - National (B-Ce), 1990 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - National (Co-Cr), 1990 (Reel 18, Frame 526)
    - National (E-W), 1990 (Reel 18, Frame 699)
    - New (S-Y), 1990 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - N-Ng, 1990 (Reel 19, Frame 376)
    - Ni-No, 1990 (Reel 19, Frame 425)
    - O, 1990 (Reel 19, Frame 745)
    - Pan American Health Organization, 1990 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - Pa-Pl, 1990 (Reel 20, Frame 166)
    - Po-Pu, 1990 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Ra-Re, 1990 (Reel 21, Frame 324)
    - Rockefeller, 1990 (Reel 21, Frame 769)
    - Rh-Ru, 1990 (Reel 21, Frame 772)
    - Sa-Sm, 1990 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - So-Sy, 1990 (Reel 22, Frame 182)
    - Ta-Tr, 1990 (Reel 22, Frame 780)
    - Tu-Tw, 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - United States (A-S), 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 289)
    - United States Committee for Refugees, 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 404)
    - United States Committee for United Nations Children's Fund, 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 479)
    - United States Information Agency (Glade, William P.), 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 484)
    - University (C-I), 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 495)
    - University (M-N), 1990 (Reel 23, Frame 712)
    - University (P-W), 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Urban Forum (Ethnicity Conference), 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 312)
    - U, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 740)
    - V, 1990 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - W-Wa, 1990 (Reel 25, Frame 228)
    - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development (A-M), 1990 (Reel 25, Frame 519)
    - We-Wi, 1990 (Reel 25, Frame 728)
    - Wo-Wy, 1990 (Reel 25, Frame 861)
    - X-Z, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - United States of America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1990; 1990/200.E
      - C-T, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 384)
  - Philippines, 1990; 1990/242
    - I-U, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 552)
  - Argentina, 1990; 1990/301
    - C, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 601)
  - Brazil, 1990; 1990/305
    - A-W, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 637)
  - Chile, 1990; 1990/309
    - Croxatto, Horacio, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 754)
  - Colombia, 1990; 1990/311
    - C-M, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 758)
  - Costa Rica, 1990; 1990/313
    - A-T, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 940)
  - Mexico, 1990; 1990/323
    - A-Z, 1990 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
  - Republic of Panama, 1990; 1990/327
    - Centro de Estudios y Capacitacion Familiar, 1990 (Reel 27, Frame 201)
  - Paraguay, 1990; 1990/329
    Paraguay
    - Gauto, Raul, 1990 (Reel 27, Frame 217)
  - Venezuela, 1990; 1990/339
    - Venezuelan Foundation for the Conservation of Biological Diversity, 1990 (Reel 27, Frame 223)
  - England, 1990; 1990/401
    - B-W, 1990 (Reel 27, Frame 225)
  - Scotland, 1990; 1990/405
    - Farries & Co., Ltd., 1990 (Reel 27, Frame 682)
  - Australia, 1990; 1990/410
    - U-V, 1990 (Reel 27, Frame 689)
  - Canada, 1990; 1990/427
    - C-W, 1990 (Reel 27, Frame 704)
  - Hong Kong, 1990; 1990/463
    - Hong Kong Institute of Asia (Pacific Studies), 1990 (Reel 27, Frame 802)
  - India, 1990; 1990/464
    - B-T, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1990; 1990/464.E
      - A-S, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 168)
  - Bengal / Bangladesh, 1990; 1990/466
    - International Center for Diarrhoeal Disease (Habte, Demissie), 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 236)
  - Africa, 1990; 1990/475
    - Population Research Organization for Eastern and Southern Africa (Declination), 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 255)
  - Kenya (British East Africa), 1990; 1990/476
    - I-U, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 257)
  - Malawi (Nyasaland), 1990; 1990/482
    - University of Malawi (Dubbey, John), 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 323)
  - Rhodesia, 1990; 1990/483
    - University of Zimbabwe (Latif, A. S.), 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 325)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1990; 1990/489
    - F-U, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 329)
  - Uganda, 1990; 1990/492
    - A-U, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 383)
  - West Africa, 1990; 1990/495
    - West Africa Rice Development Association, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 403)
  - Nigeria, 1990; 1990/497
    - D-O, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 411)
  - Sierra Leone, 1990; 1990/499
    - Maddy, Y. A., 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 496)
  - France, 1990; 1990/500
    - E-U, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 501)
  - Ivory Coast, 1990; 1990/527
    - S-W, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 516)
  - Senegal, 1990; 1990/531
    - A-C, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 583)
  - Yemen, 1990; 1990/575
    Yemen
    - Farag, Abdelmegid M., 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 605)
  - People's Republic of China, 1990; 1990/601
    - C-X, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 633)
    - People's Republic of China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1990; 1990/601.E
      - L-T, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 712)
  - Japan, 1990; 1990/609
    - F-U, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 808)
  - Thailand, 1990; 1990/617
    - M-P, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 887)
  - Holland, 1990; 1990/650
    - B-U, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 946)
  - Indonesia, 1990; 1990/652
    - Chirgwin, M., 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 1017)
  - Europe, 1990; 1990/700
    Europe
    - E, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 1019)
  - Ethiopia, 1990; 1990/701
    - International Livestock Centre for Africa (Fitzhugh, Hank A.), 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 1027)
  - Belgium, 1990; 1990/707
    - University of Louvain (Gerard, Hubert), 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 1033)
  - Denmark, 1990; 1990/713
    - Carlsberg Research Center (Mundy, John), 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 1049)
  - Germany, 1990; 1990/717
    - Institute for Advanced Study, Berlin, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 1057)
  - Tanganyika (Zambia), 1990; 1990/723
    - University of Dar es Salaam (M-S), 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 1066)
  - Zambia, 1990; 1990/724
    - E-U, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
  - Cameroon, 1990; 1990/735
    - C-U, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 9)
  - Togo, 1990; 1990/745
    - D-U, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 14)
  - Italy, 1990; 1990/751
    - G-S, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 84)
  - Liberia, 1990; 1990/759
    - University of Liberia (Demography), 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 199)
  - Morocco, 1990; 1990/765
    - Institut Agramique et Veterinaire Hassan II, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 201)
  - Portugal, 1990; 1990/773
    - Forum de Danca, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 204)
  - Russia, 1990; 1990/785
    - B-S, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 206)
  - Sweden, 1990; 1990/800
    - Swedish Agency for Research Cooperation (Bolme, Per), 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 222)
  - Switzerland, 1990; 1990/803
    - C-D, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 234)
  - Turkey, 1990; 1990/805
    - Yolcuogly, Burhan, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 279)
  - Palestine / Israel, 1990; 1990/825
    - J-W, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 283)
  - Members and Meetings, 1990; 1990/903
    - C-J, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 425)
  - Humanities, 1990; 1990/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1990; 1990/911.E
      - 911E, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 481)
      - S-U, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 487)
  - Publicity and Publications, 1990; 1990/912
    - Publicity and Publications - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1990; 1990/912.E
      - 912E, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 591)
  - Division of Studies, 1990; 1990/913
    - Division of Studies - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1990; 1990/913.E
      - 913E, 1990 (Reel 29, Frame 608)